Uh, hello. I'm Alessandro. I'm a product
manager at Amazon in Paris.
My main job is running integrations for
EU accounts uh
with more than 100 million annual
revenues.
Uh, before that I finished a master's
degree
at ESCP Business School where I built a
a machine learning model for startup
evaluations uh beating the the
benchmarking venture capital market. Uh,
what makes me an outlier is that
everyone up here wants to be the the
founder, the pitcher of of
for the company.
Uh, this is not my case.
What I actually good is breaking down
data um
and making them clear to to take
decisions. I prefer to be the operator
to to run the machine and the the data,
the finance, everything
to reach the goal
together with with with colleagues.
Um,
I Moreover, I I I got 100,000 euro on my
own savings. Uh, what I'm missing more
is a commercial person to that wants to
sell my my product on what or what I
build to the market.